Hi.
How are you?  Thank you.  [laughter] Let's
say thank you.  What is?
So mom, how did you feel after meeting your modern daughter-in-law?
If I had brought a modern daughter-in-law, you would have
seen her like this.
Beautiful.  What do you do?  What to do?
[laughs]
Let's meet Amma.
Amma mi hope this.   Thank
you.
Hey guys good morning.  Welcome to my new
vlog.  So today's video is going to be very interesting.
Because look at this today brother, today
Avantika has become a completely modern wife for a day, just like the ones from
foreign countries,
Avantika is going to talk like that too.   The
whole day I spend with my family, with a foreign
girl, not with an English
girl.  She is going to react like this.   Yes.
So let's see what kind of experience
everyone has.
Hmm
ready?  Ready?  Will give the family the
experience of what if you get married to
a foreign girl.   Yes.   It went over
my head.  Listen.
Hmm
guys, look Avantika's dress up is also completely like that of a
modern girl.  Let me
show you the whole thing first.
And also I behave like a modern wife
and a modern daughter in love for today.   Please
talk to me in Hindi.  Hey, I am
saying that today we are going to give the family the
experience that if you had done a
love marriage and you had
married a dangerous girl who was so
modern these days, then yes, how would the
family have felt, what would have been their
experience because right now you have
brought it in your culture, daughter-in-law, hmm, so
they accept it, what if you,
but if you would have got married to a, you know,
foreigner,
then look at Avantiya's glasses, look at Avantiya's
clothes, there is a flower here, look at the neck
and what is this?  Look this
is tile you know my accessories
you [nasal voice] won't get it I know
and look brother with the full heel wheel yes
Avantika has got a different look today
brother it is going to be a lot of fun because I am
not able to understand what Avantika is saying
what will the family understand so but guys
this is just for fun do
n't judge like this I want to give an experience
that if you had done this brother what would have happened at
home so let's go
down and see the reaction of the family
how does mom react
seeing the guy like this I am
going to meet you you man welcome welcome
thank you
elder mom is here mom someone has come to meet you
who is coming today
your modern daughter in law
yes
modern daughter in law has come hi how are
you
thank you
thank you what do you say
what are you saying I am not able to understand how are
you how are
you [laughs]
hi hi
so nice me thank you for you
thank you
[laughs]
what happened
what happened she is laughing am  I am looking funny
she meeting for the first time any modern
girl any foreigner isnt
she comfortable with me comfortable ho?   She is
saying that she has eaten it, what are you saying to me
?   Are you
eating, haven't you eaten, are you comfortable?
Hey, I'm yes comfortable.
Talk to me, mom.
What should I talk about?  He is not able to understand what I am saying.
What is she saying I am not able to
understand?  Could you please translate for
me?
They don't understand what you are saying
?
She was saying that she had eaten her food.
No
What is she saying?
She saying
yes, have
you eaten something?
No [laughter] he was saying you cook food for me
today so I don't understand she saying go she saying she doesn't understand you it's okay it's okay
she has a beautiful smile
oh my god what she's
laughing mead [laughter] you you don't like
this flower you don't like this where did you get this from
?
Where did you get it from?
I just but this is me meeting you for the
first time.
[laughs]
I don't have enough for
everyone in the fold. I got 11 members
in the family.  So flowers for everyone.
[laughter]
She says she brought it for everyone.  I am 11
people.  I have brought a flower for everyone.   She is
speaking like this.
Okay
you did touch her feet
touching feet
or you
touch her feet
why it's
our tradition in
touching feet
or you touch oh
touching
hey [laughs] not like this you just you just
touch your feet like this take her take her
blessing
[laughs]
hey there is a foot girl right my
yes foot girl
oh you you came with sandals
or
why?
It's It is
not allowed here.  Just
how is it going?
U turn off sandals?
Take off sandals?
Oh do I need to
take off my sandals?  My my
first foot will get dirty if I I will take them off.
What do you want to meet?
What?
What are you saying?  My home is dirty.   From
what only?
What happened?  Yes, I
fell
if you fail,
no, I am heavy of that [laughs]
where are you, other family members and where
is your dad, I am so excited to meet your
dad, I have heard so much about him from you,
my dad is at market, he will come, he will come after one hour, so
Ammi, how did you like meeting the
modern daughter-in-law, if I had brought a modern daughter-in-law, it would have been like this,
then see how we speak, while speaking, how would we
ask something, friend, I have not been able to understand anything.
She's saying something about me that I'm bad.   No no
you are not bad.
[laughter]
What is she saying, bed bed?  bed
bed no
she's saying that I I'm dirty.
Mom, am I saying this?
Oh no, I said bed bed whatever she's saying
[laughs].
No, not this bed.   She is saying that she has
moved the bed, I said.   She's
so sweet.
sweet?
Or
you are sweet, Bal.  Good?   Or.
Dude you like the flower?
Sweet means good.
Hmm.
[laughter]
Why is she smiling unnecessarily?  [laughter]
I did know what's going on?  Can you please
explain me as well?
She is confused what to do, what to say
?  O be comfortable
[laughs] no worry
yes I am comfortable sitting here
no [laughs]
I am saying be comfortable with me
excuse me have a call ok some urgent
calls
hello
see mummy this would have happened if modern bahu had
brought one from
somewhere outside I would not have been able to understand what you are
saying I would
not have been able to understand thank you thank you so much you are
sorry [laughs] it was call
you want to meet our aunt what is there what
aunt
you are second
what will you say second mother in law
you are two moms.
or I have to no two moms then
no no
aunty it's it's aunty aunty
no aunty that she
is my aunty
your aunty she with you
or or
your aunty I want to meet her as well okay okay
let me call her oh
that's for you have 11 members you told
me
aunty has anyone come to meet you?  Come, has anyone come to
meet you?  come soon.  Oh she is aunty.
Hi Hi
Beautiful Thank you Thank you so much even he is
beautiful what do you do what to do
[laughs]
than of me
Papa wale samjh hi nahi aami rahi [laughs] what is
your routine what is your routine
humko English samjh nahi aama rahi they don't have
any routine what is the saying?
[laughter]
What is the model saying?  Daughter-in-law
is asking you what is your routine?  She is asking
me how do I know about our roti, so
make roti [laughs]
eating vegetables, sleeping is the
routine roti [laughs]
roti
routine is the same every day right now sweeping and
mopping [laughs]
[sudden sound of heavy breathing] washing clothes
he will not understand Hindi
and you told me you live with your
grandparents as well
or you want to meet my grandparents you you want to meet
Amma
yes what Amma
Amma is grand mother
oh or or I want to meet your grand let's go yes come let's go
what happened should
I also come [laughs]
what are you saying don't meet grand mother
no no they are saying they want to come
joint [sound of clearing throat] not joint
friend don't say joint [laughs] friend
don't say joint do you
know what is joint?
[screaming]
Or you have a joint family.
Or [laughs] guys,
this looks so real because
they really don't understand
what Avantiya is saying.  So they are definitely giving real reactions.
Let's meet Amma
Amma Amma or [laughs]
Hi
where are you from?  This is
oh thank you thank you how are
you how are you how are
you
[laughter]
I'm fine say I'm
fine I'm fine it's
great hello this is oh
how are you what are you doing what are you saying what are you saying
what are you doing
[laughter]
I'm doing great.
Amma is very famous.
It's great.  It's great.
Where do you come from?   Where you come
from?
I am from England.
England.
England.   Let us go.   You have
come alone.
She is my wife.
What happened?  Mom, why aren't you saying anything
?  You calmed down.   I do
n't know English.  what to say  Curry
rice.  You will have kadhi chawal?  We are making
kadhi rice.
Ok.
That's your traditional food.
Or
I vote a lot about India's foods, they are tasty and
delicious.  What are you making me do,
Kadhi?
Curry rice.
Curry rice.   Do
you know curry?  What is Kadhi?
This is curry.
Oh this is curry.   Yes.
Guys are acting very strong.  It
looks as if someone has come from outside.
Really, she doesn't seem like Avantika from the
way she talks.  What's his name?
Oreo
Oreo Hi Oreo
Kunali has come from school.
Kunal my little brother has come.
Hi
Swarada who is this?
This is your sister-in-law.
Bhabhi, how are
you?
How are you?   It
seems to you that it came from the British.
How are you?   Please
reply.  You must know English.
English?
Yes.  do it.   A
little means I don't know that much.
Then you can reply how you too.
He doesn't know how to say anything in Hindi.
No, it does
n't come in Hindi.
No she is from England.
Coming from school in England.  Are you coming from
school?
You are a V standard?
What is standard?  Tell me, tell me.
Don't you know the standard?   Please
tell.
In which school?  What is this?
Tell me, tell me something.
She is asking which class are you in?
Good class.  In fourth class means for
you.   Thank
you.  Guys, the food is ready.  This is
curry and this is rice and this is cucumber.
Kadhi Rice Tasty Kadhi Rice.
You also have.
I have this also.
You also have, whatever
I am
saying,
you should also eat it.
Well, it's
really delicious.
Never eaten [laughter]?
What happened?
Phrygian.   No no no no.
Ever since Avantika has become a modern daughter-in-law, she has
not become normal, not even once is she
talking normally, she is talking to
us like this, she is talking to me like this,
now why,
now become normal,
it's Arsi and I really,
hey become normal, listen I am saying, become
normal now,
I am really amazed by the hospitality
[laughs] or
hospital,
not hospital, what is hospitality,
now get out of this character, your mother is waiting for you to
talk to her in Hindi,
become our Pahadi daughter-in-law.  It's enough.   It's enough.
Come to Pahadi Bahu.
We will not be able to tolerate this for long.   I wo
n't be able to tolerate it for long.
[Sound of clearing throat]
So guys, we were just doing all this for fun
so that we could
give our family an experience of what would happen.  What would
happen?
We have come Papa ji.  Papa ji, someone is coming to
meet you.  What happened?  Why did you stop?
Your modern daughter-in-law has come to meet you.   Yes
?
Yes.   Hi! How Are
You?
Hi thank you
I was talking about you all this time where are
you?
Okay [laughs] He
's giving me the same flowers I give to you,
Mom. [laughs]
Okay, these are some given to everyone.  So this is
for you, thank
you, thank you, how are you, I am fine, you know, how
long I was waiting for you, you were at
the market,
or
you went shopping, did you understand, I understood, are you going
from the market, are you coming back
from the market, after roaming around and
shopping,
very nice, how do you think you are, you are having
lunch,
or it was very delicious [laughs],
cowrie rice,
what
if mom is saying like this, if it had come like this, brother,
I would not have been able to stay, no, no, then
why,
I am not able to understand,
yes, she must be doing it because of speaking,
yes, because of speaking, I am saying,
okay, if she does not understand, then
you do not have any problem, what
problem do I have, friend, it is good, in fact,
we will also learn a little,
Papa ji is right, isn't it, friend, Papa ji [laughs]
oh tell me, only when he tells, we will learn,
friend, does anyone tell us the address, no, what are you saying,
how will it happen, then tell me, will I tell you,
he is saying like this,
next time I will bring some good
dresses for your mom, your,
no, no, I will bring a dress, well,
Papa ji  I am understanding friend
you are talking lightly no Hindi
oh no no
only for English
or I told your son my husband I
learn Hindi for you guys
ok ok
I will learn it will take time definitely because
I am learning something it will take
time but what are your hobbies what do you do hobby is theek hi hai
humare [laughs]
oh tappu I have brought oh oh lna
lna
snake hi se lna this is
mango
wo snake samjhegi aise kya laan laan dekho kya lna yes lna accha
sabji baareez haan yes do you know
lna sabji that is forest
vegetable I don't know I don't no
yes bring it show me
in our jungle there is a vegetable called lna
and it looks like snake
oh snake
or it looks like
you eat snake no no no that is not
snake that that is a vegetable that
looks like snake and that is vegetable
ok ok also want
to taste  That vegetable
or
I told you saying your mom and dad it's
snakes
no no no no
she is continuously smiling
and laughing smiling laughing
what happened to you
no what's going on [laughs]
Jwala what I am finding myself funny
Lana
thank you this is Lana Lana this is vegetable this is
vegetable oh Lana
or this is it
looking like a snake
or this looking like a snake
or forest vegetable
ghadre wali this
is a mango beautiful mango mango
my god mango
1 kg plus 1 kg plus 1
kg mango
plus we can use it as a dumbbell [laughs]
wow
show me show me the
whole family will eat
this
[laughs] the
whole
family can eat this isko ek baar mein
kat kar yes yaar guys
small-chote pieces bana iske bhaiya mere
haath bhi kitna bada mango hai
bhaiya 1 kg se ek
bhaiya sahab brother first time dekha itna bada mango hako it
Was really lovely meeting all the family
members, this is so sweet.
I enjoyed meeting everyone.
Ok.  I enjoyed meeting everyone.
Okay, okay, thank you, thank you.  Thank you.   Thank
you.
This is my family.
Or
nice to meet you.   Say
it or
say it.  Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.  What is your name?
Oh my name.  My name is Anna.
Anna
[laughs]
Avantia's Sham
Okay
short name is Good Good
Good This is Khaan
to Me
Ya So
We're Ending the Vogue Now I Hope You Guys
Like It Thank You So Much for Watching Bye Bye
[Music]